{
    "quiz": {
        "question": [
            {
                "id": 313,
                "_id": "13-01",
                "chapterId": 13,
                "question": "What are the four phases of program evaluation?",
                "refPage": "299",
                "possible0": "Formative, Process, Outcome, Impact",
                "possible1": "Identify, Develop, Coordinate, Modify",
                "possible2": "Brainstorm, Develop, Implement, Evaluate",
                "possible3": "Storming, Forming, Norming, Performing",
                "correctAnswer": 0,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 314,
                "_id": "13-02",
                "chapterId": 13,
                "question": "What phase of program evaluation involves developing an education program (or modifying an existing one) based on the Community Risk Assessment (CRA)?",
                "refPage": "299",
                "possible0": "Impact",
                "possible1": "Process",
                "possible2": "Outcome",
                "possible3": "Formative",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 315,
                "_id": "13-03",
                "chapterId": 13,
                "question": "What phase of program evaluation involves counting education program activities, so that the who, when, what, where, and why of each activity is captured?",
                "refPage": "300",
                "possible0": "Formation",
                "possible1": "Identification",
                "possible2": "Modification",
                "possible3": "Process/Implementation",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 316,
                "_id": "13-04",
                "chapterId": 13,
                "question": "What phase of program evaluation determines whether the education program’s ultimate goals have been achieved?",
                "refPage": "300",
                "possible0": "Review",
                "possible1": "Impact",
                "possible2": "Outcome",
                "possible3": "Implement",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 317,
                "_id": "13-05",
                "chapterId": 13,
                "question": "What phase of program evaluation determines whether change (to what degree) – in knowledge, behavior, or public policy – has occurred?",
                "refPage": "300",
                "possible0": "Modify",
                "possible1": "Impact",
                "possible2": "Process",
                "possible3": "Outcome",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 318,
                "_id": "13-06",
                "chapterId": 13,
                "question": "What are the three phases of risk reduction?",
                "refPage": "301",
                "possible0": "Review, modify, impact",
                "possible1": "Storming, norming, performing",
                "possible2": "Primary prevention, secondary prevention, tertiary prevention",
                "possible3": "Identify the problem, correlate resources, account for actions",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 319,
                "_id": "13-07",
                "chapterId": 13,
                "question": "What step for developing an injury surveillance system involves determining the pertinent details, which include demographic information such as age, location, nature of injuries, and any other information relevant to the outcome of the program?",
                "refPage": "302",
                "possible0": "Using the results",
                "possible1": "Collecting the data",
                "possible2": "Defining the problem",
                "possible3": "Evaluating the system",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 320,
                "_id": "13-08",
                "chapterId": 13,
                "question": "What attribute of good surveillance systems, as identified by the World Health Organization, refers to anyone using the data should have complete confidence in the accuracy of the information?",
                "refPage": "303",
                "possible0": "Utility",
                "possible1": "Reliability",
                "possible2": "Acceptability",
                "possible3": "Sustainability",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 321,
                "_id": "13-09",
                "chapterId": 13,
                "question": "What agency has used surveillance systems to provide information about behaviors relating to health and injury, including the Behavioral Risk Factor Surveillance System?",
                "refPage": "304",
                "possible0": "World Health Organization",
                "possible1": "National Fire Data Center",
                "possible2": "Federal Emergency Management Agency",
                "possible3": "Centers for Disease Control and Prevention",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 322,
                "_id": "13-10",
                "chapterId": 13,
                "question": "What are pieces of information collected from an evaluation that can numerically describe the results of the risk-reduction process?",
                "refPage": "305",
                "possible0": "Insight",
                "possible1": "Benchmarks",
                "possible2": "Qualitative data",
                "possible3": "Quantitative data",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 323,
                "_id": "13-11",
                "chapterId": 13,
                "question": "What type of evaluation answers the questions “How do you quantify that?”, “How many?” or “How much?” and uses numbers as the basis for the analysis process?",
                "refPage": "305",
                "possible0": "Analysis",
                "possible1": "Qualitative",
                "possible2": "Interpretive",
                "possible3": "Quantitative",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 324,
                "_id": "13-12",
                "chapterId": 13,
                "question": "What type of evaluation is used to answer the questions “What are the qualities involved?”, “How?” and “Why?” and evaluates people’s attitudes and opinions, mainly in narrative form?",
                "refPage": "305",
                "possible0": "Qualitative",
                "possible1": "Quantitative",
                "possible2": "Benchmarking",
                "possible3": "Accomplishment",
                "correctAnswer": 0,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 325,
                "_id": "13-13",
                "chapterId": 13,
                "question": "What term refers to a short term or interim accomplishment toward an objective?",
                "refPage": "306",
                "possible0": "Watermark",
                "possible1": "Benchmark",
                "possible2": "Progression",
                "possible3": "Implementation",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            }
        ]
    }
}
